我告诉你  如果氙能放射出紫外线
I'm telling you, if xenon emits ultraviolet light,
那些有关暗物质的发现都会是错的
then those dark matter discoveries must be wrong.
那是  如果我们住在一个
Yes, well, if we lived in a world
缓慢运动的氙原子能放出光子的世界
where slow-moving xenon produced light,
那你就是对的
then you'd be correct.
与此同时  猪能飞
Also, pigs would fly,
我也能拉出棉花糖来
my derriere would produce cotton candy,
而《幽灵的威胁》也将成为永恒的经典
and The Phantom Menace would be a timeless classic.
你也太傲慢了
Oh, you're so arrogant.
如果你是超级英雄
If you were a superhero,
那你的名字就该叫傲慢上尉
your name would be Captain Arrogant.
你知道你的超能力是什么吗
And you know what your superpower would be?
傲慢力
Arrogance.
你又错了
You're wrong again.
如果我的超能力是傲慢力
If my superpower were arrogance,
我的名字应该是至傲博士
my name would be Dr. Arroganto.
我太喜欢看拉杰和谢尔顿一块儿工作了
I love watching Raj and Sheldon try to work together.
没错  就好比异形和铁血战士决定
Yeah, it's like if Alien and Predator decided
合作开一间Jamba Juice一样
to go partners in a Jamba Juice.
你难道没注意宏观的状况吗
Has it occurred to you you're missing the big picture?
-如果你看了中子分布数据  -佩妮
- If you look at neutron scattering data...  - Oh, Penny?
-佩妮  -怎么了
- Penny?  - What's up?
没事儿  我只是想让拉杰闭嘴而已
Nothing. I just wanted to make Raj stop talking.
不不不
No, no, no.
他赢了  憋着吧
He won. Suck it up.
我想问问你们是否需要甜品
Well, I'd ask you guys if you want dessert,
但我知道谢尔顿周二不吃甜品
but I know Sheldon doesn't eat dessert on Tuesdays.
而拉杰就算想要什么也开不了口
And even if Raj wanted something, he couldn't tell me.
霍华德什么都不会点
Howard won't order anything,
但他会迸出来一些跟派或者芝士蛋糕
but he will come up with some sort of skeevy comment
有关系的恶心话
involving the words pie or cheesecake.
而莱纳德有乳糖不耐
And Leonard's lactose intolerant,
所以除非他想让自己的肠子
so he can't eat anything here
涨得跟动物气球似的  否则是什么都吃不了的
without his intestines blowing up like a balloon animal.
等等
Hang on a second.
我可以点水果拼盘的
I could have the fruit platter.
你想要水果拼盘
You want the fruit platter?
-上面有甜瓜吗  -有
- Does it have melon on it?  - Yeah.
呃  我不能吃甜瓜
No, I can't eat melon.
霍华德  注意了
Oh, Howard, heads up.
你的前女友来上班了
Your ex-girlfriend just came in for her shift.
你上次见她是什么时候
When was the last time you saw her?
分手之后就没见过了
Oh, not since we broke up.
嗯  我该怎么表现呢
Wow. How am I going to play this?
优雅而自然的
Sophisticated and relaxed?
还是友好而含糊的
Friendly, noncommittal?
或者冷淡且陌生的
Cold and distant?
你们好
Hi, guys.
你好
Hello.
看来你决定用悲剧和惊恐来面对了
I see you decided to go with pathetic and frightened.
这是他的拿手好戏
It's one of his best moves.
生活大爆炸
第四季第四集
亲爱的  我们又见面了
So, my dear, we meet again.
好啊  霍华德
Hello, Howard.
我想你了
I've missed you.
我也想你了  凯蒂·萨克霍夫
I've missed you, Katee Sackhoff.
-问个问题  -随便问
- One question.  - Anything.
为什么我会在床上穿着《太空堡垒卡拉狄加》的战斗服
Why am I wearing my Battlestar Galactica flight suit in bed?
那你又为什么你会和我同床呢
Why are you in bed with me?
如果我们开始质疑这个  那就太崩溃了
If we start to question this, it all falls apart.
不好意思
Sorry.
噢  强力地占有我吧  霍华德
Oh, ravish me, Howard.
我愿为你尽折腰
My loins ache for you.
好吧  既然你如此坚持的话
Okay, if you insist.
霍华德  你看到我的束腹紧身裤了吗
Howard, have you seen my girdle?!
没有  妈
No, Ma!
我找不着了  而且减肥族大会就快要迟到了
I can't find it, and I'm late for my Weight Watchers meeting!
也许它自杀了
Maybe it committed suicide!
少烦我
Leave me alone!
好了  刚才到哪儿了
Now, where were we?
我觉得你想要
I believe you were about
用你的牙齿扒下我的制服了
to rip off my uniform with your teeth.
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?!
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我猜的话  估计是
Well, if I had to guess, I'd say I'm here
因为你今晚见到我了
because you saw me earlier this evening,
而你还对我有留恋
and you're still hung up on me.
才没有呢
No, I'm not.
很明显有
Clearly you are.
否则根据以往经验
Otherwise, based on past experience,
我们现在都该完事儿了
we'd be done by now.
好吧  我现在有点混乱了
Okay, I'm a little confused here.
亲爱的  我能帮什么吗
Oh, my. Can I help?
又不是那方面的困惑
Not that kind of confused.
武井乔治在这儿干嘛
What's George Takei doing here?
霍华德  你有隐性的同性恋倾向吗
Howard, do you have latent homosexual tendencies?
当然没有了
No, of course not.
你是这么说了
So you say.
而我却站在这儿了
Yet, here I am.
乔治  我问你个问题
George, let me ask you something.
作为科幻人物象征你是如何应对连续出演同类角色的
How did you deal with being typecast as a science fiction icon?
是很难
It's difficult.
作为演员你想拓展戏路
You try and stretch as an actor--
尝试下斯特林堡  奥尼尔什么的
do Strindberg, O'Neill,
但他们想要的只是"航线已设定  船长"
but all they want is, "Course laid in, Captain."
好好跟我说说
Tell me about it.
这太让我抓狂了
It's frackin' frustrating.
等等  凯蒂  你怎么走了
Wait. Katee, why are you leaving?
她走了是因为你内心深处想和我一起啊
She's leaving because you really want to be with me.
霍华德  我找到我的束腹紧身裤了
Howard, I found my girdle!
原来在烘干机里
It was in the dryer!
那太好了  妈妈
Great, Ma!
我觉得它缩水了
I think it shrunk!
我的赘肉就跟面团宝宝似的
I'm spilling out like the Pillsbury Doughboy here!
一想到那个画面
And with that mental picture,
我想今晚的精神治疗到此为止了
I think we're done for the evening.
你从没跟我说过你和伯纳黛特当初为何分手
You never told me what happened between you and Bernadette.
我做了件蠢事
I did a stupid thing.
我猜也是
Yeah, I guessed that.
像是那种现在难以面对她的蠢事
It was the kind of thing that makes it kind of hard to face her now.
你说的这范围广的可以从被窝里放屁
That covers anything from farting in bed
延伸到杀害流浪汉
to killing a homeless guy.
哦  我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你真碾死过流浪汉啊
You ran over a hobo.
没有  别问了
No. Stop asking.
好吧  你想跟她重归于好
All right, fine. So you want to get back together with her,
但却羞于面对她
but you're too ashamed to face her
就因为你曾经做了某件难以启齿的事
because of whatever it is you did.
-差不多  -好吧
- In a nutshell. - Okay.
那这么做你觉得怎样
Well, how about this?
你戴上诡异的面具从剧院里
Kidnap Bernadette from the opera
把伯纳黛特劫走  这样她就认不出你了
wearing a creepy mask so she doesn't know it's you.
这么说吧  我不知道你是在跟我开玩笑还是怎么着
Now, you see, I don't know if you're kidding or not.
你开始蛮横无理了
You're being unreasonable.
为什么我就不能有张桌子
Why can't I have a desk?!
我们的合作研究是思维上的工作
Our collaboration is a work of the mind.
我们用不着桌子
We don't need desks.
但你有桌子啊
You have a desk.
-是的  -但我就不能有了是吧
- Correct. - But I can't have one.
你说中要点了
You're two for two.
为什么他不能有桌子  谢尔顿
Why can't he have a desk, Sheldon?
天呐  这一天怎么过不完了
Oh, Lord, will this day never end?
我已经再三向库萨帕里博士解释过了
As I've explained repeatedly to Dr. Koothrappali,
以他对美国俗语的理解能力  是不能明白
whose ability to comprehend the American idiom fails him
什么叫做时机妥当的
when it's convenient.
我的预算中绝没有添置额外办公家具的那份了
There's absolutely no money in my budget for additional office furniture.
那你就有预算来买一抽屉的红蜡糖
Oh, but there's money for a drawer full of Red Vines,
一把棉花糖步枪
a marshmallow shooting rifle,
以及带有夜光沙土的超级蚂蚁工坊[玩具]吗
and a super executive ant farm with glow-in-the-dark sand?
是的
Yes.
好吧  那他出钱买自己的桌子呢
Okay, what if he buys his own desk?
是啊  要是我买我自己的桌子呢
Yeah, what if I buy my own desk?
-那太荒谬了  -为什么
- That's ridiculous. - Why?
因为...
Because...
请说
Yes?
这是我的办公室
It's my office.
-谢尔顿  -好了  好了
- Sheldon. - All right, all right.
他可以买他自己的桌子了
He can buy his own desk.
而且我可以放进你的办公室里
And I can put it in your office?
你还真的想得寸进尺了  是吧
Well, you really want to dot the I's and cross the T's, don't you?
为何你要买带夜光沙土的蚂蚁工坊呢
Why would you want a glow-in-the-dark ant farm?
因为蚂蚁有些工作晚上做更出色
They do some of their best work at night.
这个还能穿
Ah, it's okay.
佩妮
Penny?
如果知道是我敲门你还会开吗
Would you have opened the door if you knew it was me?
自从我发现
Not since I found out
你给我的泰迪熊安了摄像头之后就不会了
the teddy bear you gave me had a webcam in it.
我只是有个问题想问
I just have a question.
伯纳黛特有跟你提起过我吗
Does Bernadette ever talk about me?
哦  当然有啊
Oh, absolutely.
-她提过吗  -当然
- She does? - Yeah, sure.
就在昨天  她还问我
Just yesterday, she asked,
为什么霍华德要躲在桌子底下
"Why is Howard hiding under the table?"
她看见了是吧
She saw that, huh?
没  没  一开始没有
Oh, no, not at first.
但在我告诉她后就...
Right after I pointed it out.
我问你点别的吧
Let me ask you something else.
她有跟谁交往吗
Is she seeing anybody?
据我所知没有吧
Oh, not that I know of.
既然说到了这个话题
Hey, while we're on the subject,
我想了解你们当初为何分手了
why did you guys break up anyway?
我觉得还是不说为好
Oh, I'd rather not say.
霍华德  你如果想得到我的帮助  就得让我知道
Howard, if you want my help, I've got to know what happened.
但说出来有些尴尬
But it's embarrassing...
是啊  我就期待着这个呢  进来吧
Yeah, that's what I'm counting on. Spill.
好吧  你听过魔兽世界吧
Okay. Well, you know World of Warcraft?
那个网络游戏吗  当然
Um, the online game? Sure.
那你可否知道
Well, did you know
游戏中的角色是可以互相发生性关系的
that the characters in the game can have sex with each other?
哦天呐  我想我有点头绪了
Oh, God. I think I see where this is going.
她叫巨魔葛林新蒂
Her name was Glissinda the Troll.
当伯纳黛特来找我的时候
Bernadette walked in on me
我们正在灵魂之桥下翻云覆雨呢
while we were doing the cyber-nasty under the Bridge of Souls.
你说的没错  这是够糗的了
Oh, you're right. That is so embarrassing.
你能跟她说说吗
Would you talk to her?
伯纳黛特还是巨魔
Bernadette or the troll?
伯纳黛特  她太生我气了
Bernadette. She was so mad at me,
她甚至都没听我的解释
she wouldn't even listen to my side of the story.
那你的解释是什么
Well, what was your side?
那个巨魔葛林新蒂只是个虚拟的女人
Well, for all we know, Glissinda the Troll wasn't even a real woman.
我是说  她也可能是个年届50在新泽西开卡车的人呢
I mean, she could've been a 50-year-old truck driver in New Jersey.
真的假的  那这么说没让她消消气吗
Really? And that didn't make her feel better?
你能帮我去问问看吗   看看我们还有没有
Will you talk to her, see if there's any chance at all
重归于好的可能性了
we could get back together?
天  霍华德  我真不想趟你俩这趟浑水
Oh, gee, Howard, I really don't want to get in the middle of this.
别啊  你怎么忍心呢
No. Why would you?
我这个孤单的书呆子  和老妈相依为命
I'm just another lonely nerd, living with his mother,
努力寻求哪怕是一丝丝的幸福
trying to find any scrap of happiness he can.
也许是为了弥补
You know, maybe to make up for
11岁时父亲就离开他的缺憾吧
the fact that his dad left him when he was 11.
好吧  我会考虑的
Okay, I will think about it.
我一直在为父亲的出走
You know, I've always blamed myself
而深深自责
for him leaving.
我一直觉得那是因为他根本不想要我这个儿子
I always thought it was because I wasn't the son he wanted.
行了  我说了我会考虑的
Yeah, I said I'd think about it.
我体育不好  又有点病怏怏的
I wasn't athletic, yeah, I was kind of sickly...
行了  好了  我在给她打电话了  看见没
Okay, fine. Look, look, I'm calling her now! See?!
谢谢
Thank you.
总之  霍华德请佩妮帮忙牵线伯纳黛特
So anyway, Howard asked Penny to talk to Bernadette,
然后她照办了
and she did,
接着伯纳黛特同意跟他见面  一起喝杯咖啡
and Bernadette agreed to meet him for a cup of coffee.
-我有个问题  -问吧
- One question.  - Yeah?
你干嘛跟我说这些
Why on earth are you telling me all this?
不知道
I don't know.
有时候你的动作如此栩栩如生
Sometimes your movements are so lifelike,
我都忘了你其实不是人
I forget you're not a real boy.
是你说我可以买张书桌的
You said I could buy a desk.
这东西压根不是书桌
This isn't a desk.
这是个...硕大无朋的怪物
This is a... Brobdingnagian monstrosity.
这是美国俗语里面对"巨大的书桌"的叫法吗
Is that the American idiom for "Giant, big-ass desk"?
其实是英式英语的说法
It's actually British.
能给我再说一遍吗
Can you say it again for me?
硕大无朋
Brobdingnagian.
再来一遍
One more time?
硕大无朋
Brobdingnagian.
来个三倍速的
Now three times fast?
硕大无朋  硕大无...
Brobdingnagian, Brobdingna...
你怎么把它给弄进来的
How did you even get it in here?
秘诀只有我  拉蒙和胡里奥  耶稣还有罗德里格知道
That's for me, Ramon, Julio, Jesus and Rodrigo to know
自己想哦
and you to find out.
好吧  你的立场明摆着了
All right, you've made your point.
很有意思的恶作剧
A fine prank, very amusing.
现在给我搬出去
Now get it out.
-不  -搬
- No.  - Yes.
- No.  - Yes!
我有仨兄弟俩姐妹  谢尔顿
I have three brothers and two sisters, Sheldon--
磨嘴皮子你休想赢我
I can do this all day.
好吧  既然你不搬
All right, if you're not going to remove it,
我来给你搬
I'll remove it for you.
请自便
Knock yourself out.
帮我搬一下我的书桌
Help me move my desk.
-不  -搬
- No.  - Yes.
不  这也过于硕大无朋了
No. It's too Brobdingnagian.
你怎么会想把这东西弄来这儿
Why do you even want this here?
它的大小与用途完全不成比例
Its size is completely disproportionate to its purpose.
要说它的用途就是让你不爽的话
Well, seeing as its purpose was to piss you off,
我看真是恰到好处
I'd say it's spot-on.
好了  我明白怎么回事了
All right, I see what's going on.
你就是公开对我宣战
This is the opening salvo in what will be
接下来就是一系列越演越烈的幼稚的针锋相对
an escalating series of juvenile tit-for-tat exchanges.
这个回合你赢了
Well titted.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
你给我走着瞧
Stand by for my upcoming tat.
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon?
什么事
Yes?
不  没事
No.
发现没  我把这两句话给转过来了
See what I did there? I turned it around.
抱歉  我得打卡下班
Sorry, I had to clock out.
没事  没关系的
Oh, no, that's okay.
你过得怎么样
How have you been?
还好了  就是忙着读书上班什么的  你呢
Okay. You know, busy, school, work. You?
一样  夏天时我选了一门戴水肺潜水的课程
Same. I took a scuba-diving course over the summer,
结果发现我很怕海
but it turns out I'm terrified of the ocean.
太糟糕了
Too bad.
你有没有认识的人
You wouldn't know anybody
想买大号儿童潜水衣的
who wants to buy a wet suit, boy's large?
算了  这不重要
Yeah, forget it. Not important.
你有跟人交往吗
So, are you seeing anyone?
-说实话  我  -嗨  在忙什么呢
- Well, to be honest, I...  - Hey, how are we doing over here?
要不要给你们点杯饮料
Can I get you something to drink?
-我不用  谢谢  -我也不用
- Not for me, thanks.  - I'm okay.
要不要点些吃的
Are you gonna want to order food?
-待会再点吧  -好的
- Maybe later.  - Okay.
那么  你在跟人交往吗
So, are you seeing anybody?
没有
No.
他问我的时候我也是这么说的
That's what I told him when he asked me.
希望这不算太冒昧吧
I hope that's not out of line.
-不  没事  -佩妮  能让我们独处一会儿吗
- No, it's fine.  - Penny, can we have a little privacy?
抱歉
Oh. I'm sorry.
你呢  你有没有跟其他人交往
What about you, have you been seeing anybody?
你知道  男人嘛
Well, you know how it is with guys.
总是有需要的
I mean, we have needs and...
这么说你在和其他女孩交往
So you've been seeing other girls?
不是真实的女孩
Well, not real girls.
你是说那个风骚的巨魔吗
Does that mean slutty trolls?
你们俩看起来很渴
You know, you look thirsty.
-我给你们拿了冰茶  -谢谢
- I brought you some iced tea.  - Thank you.
这是百香果  本店新品哦
It's passion fruit, new on the menu.
-我知道  我在这上班呢  -抱歉
- I know. I work here.  - Oh, sorry.
你说得对  这不明摆着嘛
Yeah, you're right. Doy.
霍华德  巨魔那事儿说不说
So, Howard, trolls yay or nay?
别老杵在这儿行吗
Isn't there somewhere else you can be?
那样我就听不着你俩聊天了
Not where I can hear you guys.
好吧  好了
Okay, fine.
我承认  在互联网的某些黑暗肮脏的角落
I'll admit, there are dark, sordid little corners of the Internet
确实有人在喃喃呼唤沃罗法师这个名字
where the name Wolowizard is whispered in hushed tones.
我去那些地方不过是因为
The only reason I go there,
我曾那样做的唯一原因
the only reason I've ever gone there
是因为我生命中一直没有真正的女友
is because I don't have a real woman in my life.
-这下你爽了  -对  能放过你们一小会了
- You happy? - Yeah, that'll hold me for a while.
霍华德  你有过真正的女友
Howard, you did have a real woman.
我当时就在隔壁房间
I was right there in the next room
而你却疯狂地撸着鼠标跟巨魔进行剧烈运动
while you were clicking that troll's brains out.
对  但我们从未...
Yeah, but we weren't...
我是说  你我从未...
I-I mean, you and I never...
上过床
Had sex?
对
Yeah.
那又是谁的错呢
Well, whose fault was that?
免费赠送的墨西哥玉米片
Complimentary nachos!
慢慢享用
You enjoy.
从未上过床  哇
Never had sex?
你什么意思  问我那是谁的错
What do you mean, whose fault was that?
我们本可以上床的
Well, we could've been having sex,
但你从未主动采取行动
but you never made the move.
我以为是你不想我采取行动的
I didn't think you wanted me to make the move.
霍华德   女孩才不会跟你这样的人约会
Howard, a girl doesn't go out with a man like you,
就你那长相  说话那德性  还有那小紧身裤
with your looks, your fancy patter and your tight hoochie pants
除非她是想让你主动采取行动的
if she's not expecting him to eventually make the move.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
妈的我早干嘛去了
Son of a bitch.
我真有点说不出口
Hey, this is a little awkward,
但经理说我无权免费赠送玉米片
but my manager says I can't actually give nachos away.
所以  谈好了记得买单啊
So... just take that when you're ready.
对  我俩谈得很愉快
Yeah, we had a really great talk,
决定重新开始约会
and we're gonna start seeing each other again.
恭喜你们
Oh, congratulations.
那你跟那巨魔分了吗
Have you broken it to the troll yet?
是佩妮告诉你的
Did Penny tell you about that?
不是  史蒂夫·帕特森说的
No. Steve Patterson told me.
设备管理部那恶心的老胖子
The greasy old fat guy in Facilities Management?
-对  -他怎么知道的
- Yeah. - How'd he know about it?
他就是巨魔葛林新蒂
He's Glissinda the troll.
抱歉兄弟  温度调节器在我这边
Sorry, dude, the thermostat's on my side of the room,
温度就定在跟孟买一样热
so it stays Mumbai hot in here
除非你关了那愚蠢的印度音乐
until you turn off that stupid Indian music!
我自然会关了音乐
I'll turn off the music
只要你处理掉那只携带着沙门氏菌的鹦鹉
when you get rid of that salmonella-ridden parakeet!
太糟了  原来谢尔顿病态地怕鸟
Oh, too bad! Sheldon's pathologically afraid of birds!
来看啊  谢尔顿  小鸟小鸟小鸟
Hey, look, Sheldon! Birdie, birdie, birdie!
我受够了  看我的棉花糖子弹  受死吧
That's it! Prepare for marshmallow death!
你也吃我一枪
Eat flaming Nerf!
话说回来...
So anyway...
你跟伯纳黛特能和好真是太好了
That's great news about you and Bernadette.
是啊  我想带她去打迷你高尔夫
Yeah. I think I'm gonna take her to miniature golf.
对你们来说  那就相当于正常的高尔夫了
Ah. I guess for you guys that's like regular golf.
笑我矮  真的吗
Short jokes? Really?
你也就比我高那么1/4英寸罢了
You're, like, a quarter of an inch taller than me.
对  记得我比你高就好
Yeah, and don't you forget it.
我过得很愉快
I had a good time.
我也是
Me, too.
跟她吻别
Kiss her good night.
好了  该来点舌吻了
All right, now a little tongue.
别轻举妄动
Hold on there.
我们才刚刚重燃爱火
We've only just rekindled the romance.
别让过早的唾液交换  破坏了这美妙一刻
Let's not sully the moment with the exchange of saliva.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
她也想要的
She wants it.
舌吻
Tongue.
看到了吧
See?
该主动出击了
Now make the move.
太快了
Too soon.
相信我  她准备好了
Trust me, she's ready.
主动出击
Make the move.
别
No, no, no.
女士都想被好好追求  慢慢献殷勤
A lady wants to be wooed,courted slowly.
你怎么知道的
How would you know?
书上看来的
I read.
听我的霍华德  是时候了
Listen to me, Howard, it's time.
主动出击  快
Make the move, now.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
是你让我主动行动的  记得吗
You said... well, the "Move," Remember?
但不是现在
Oh, not now.
我们才刚重新开始
We're starting a new relationship.
我还需要重新了解你
I need to get to know you again.
不用重新了解的
No, you don't.
我还是我呀
It's me.
说话这副德性  还身穿小紧身裤的
The lusty charmer with the fancy patter
风流小可爱
and the hoochie pants.
耐心点  总有那么一天的
Be patient; we'll get there.
我就说嘛
Told you.
天  这什么味
Oh, God, what's that smell?
有事吗
Yes?
你们在那里面干嘛呢
What are you doing in there?
我正在制造硫化氢和氨气
I'm making hydrogen sulfide and ammonia gas.
只是个防治害虫的小实验罢了
Just a little experiment in pest control.
对付我没用的  兄弟  我可是在印度长大的
It's not gonna work, dude; I grew up in India--
那整片次大陆上  牛儿满大街乱窜
an entire subcontinent where cows walk in the street,
就没个人能有过正常的"肠胃运动"
and nobody has ever had a solid bowel movement.
那就看看你还能坚持多久
Well, we'll just see how long you can hold out.
那我们就来看看你的有害气体
Well, we'll just see how your noxious gas
跟我的肉桂苹果芳香蜡烛  哪个更厉害
fares against my cinnamon-apple-scented aroma therapy candles.
你不是说你在制造硫化氢气体
Didn't you say you're making hydrogen sulfide gas?
-没错  -那不是很易燃的吗
- Yes. - Isn't that flammable?
极易燃
Highly.
哦天哪
Oh, dear.
这事跟你没完
This is not over.